Finding Aid for University of Michigan News and Information Services Photographs, 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series J (University Record Photographic Prints) 1987-1998
  - June 19, 1989 (Box J1)
  - July 3, 1989 (Box J1)
  - July 17, 1989 (Box J1)
  - July 31, 1989 (Box J1)
  - August 14, 1989 (Box J1)
  - September 5, 1989 (Box J1)
  - September 11, 1989 (Box J1)
  - September 18, 1989 (Box J1)
  - September 25, 1989 (Box J1)
  - October 2, 1989 (Box J1)
  - October 9, 1989 (Box J1)
  - October 23, 1989 (Box J1)
  - October 30, 1989 (Box J1)
  - November 6, 1989 (Box J1)
  - November 13, 1989 (Box J1)
  - November 20, 1989 (Box J1)
  - December 4, 1989 (Box J2)
  - December 18, 1989 (Box J2)
  - January 8, 1990 (Box J2)
  - January 15, 1990 (Box J2)
  - January 22, 1990 (Box J2)
  - January 29, 1990 (Box J2)
  - February 5, 1990 (Box J2)
  - February 12, 1990 (Box J2)
  - February 19, 1990 (Box J2)
  - February 26, 1990 (Box J2)
  - March 12, 1990 (Box J2)
  - March 19, 1990 (Box J2)
  - March 26, 1990 (Box J2)
  - April 2, 1990 (Box J2)
  - April 9, 1990 (Box J2)
  - April 16, 1990 (Box J2)
  - April 23, 1990 (Box J2)
  - May 7, 1990 (Box J2)
  - May 21, 1990 (Box J2)
  - June 4, 1990 (Box J2)
  - June 18, 1990 (Box J2)
  - July 2, 1990 (Box J2)
  - July 16, 1990 (Box J2)
  - July 30, 1990 (Box J2)
  - September 4, 1990 (Box J2)
  - September 10, 1990 (Box J2)
  - September 17, 1990 (Box J2)
  - September 24, 1990 (Box J2)
  - October 1, 1990 (Box J2)
  - October 8, 1990 (Box J2)
  - October 15, 1990 (Box J2)
  - October 22, 1990 (Box J2)
  - October 29, 1990 (Box J2)
  - November 5, 1990 (Box J2)
  - November 12, 1990 (Box J2)
  - November 19, 1990 (Box J2)
  - December 3, 1990 (Box J2)
  - December 10, 1990 (Box J2)
  - December 17, 1990 (Box J2)
  - January 7, 1991 (Box J2)
  - January 14, 1991 (Box J2)
  - January 21, 1991 (Box J2)
  - January 28, 1991 (Box J2)
  - February 4, 1991 (Box J2)
  - February 11, 1991 (Box J2)
  - February 18, 1991 (Box J2)
  - March 4, 1991 (Box J2)
  - March 11, 1991 (Box J2)
  - March 18, 1991 (Box J2)
  - March 25, 1991 (Box J2)
  - April 1, 1991 (Box J3)
  - April 8, 1991 (Box J3)
  - April 15, 1991 (Box J3)
  - April 22, 1991 (Box J3)
  - May 13, 1991 (Box J3)
  - May 28, 1991 (Box J3)
  - June 10, 1991 (Box J3)
  - June 24, 1991 (Box J3)
  - July 15, 1991 (Box J3)
  - July 29, 1991 (Box J3)
  - August 19, 1991 (Box J3)
  - September 3, 1991 (Box J3)
  - September 9, 1991 (Box J3)
  - September 16, 1991 (Box J3)
  - September 23, 1991 (Box J3)
  - September 30, 1991 (Box J3)
  - October 21, 1991 (Box J3)
  - October 28, 1991 (Box J3)
  - November 4, 1991 (Box J3)
  - November 18, 1991 (Box J3)
  - November 25, 1991 (Box J3)
  - December 9, 1991 (Box J3)
  - December 16, 1991 (Box J3)
  - January 13, 1992 (Box J3)
  - January 20, 1992 (Box J3)
  - February 3, 1992 (Box J3)
  - February 17, 1992 (Box J3)
  - March 2, 1992 (Box J3)
  - March 16, 1992 (Box J3)
  - March 23, 1992 (Box J3)
  - March 30, 1992 (Box J3)
  - April 6, 1992 (Box J3)
  - April 20, 1992 (Box J3)
  - May 4, 1992 (Box J3)
  - May 18, 1992 (Box J3)
  - June 8, 1992 (Box J3)
  - June 22, 1992 (Box J3)
  - July 6, 1992 (Box J3)
  - July 20, 1992 (Box J3)
  - August 16, 1992 (Box J3)
  - August 17, 1992 (Box J3)
  - September 8, 1992 (Box J3)
  - September 14, 1992 (Box J3)
  - September 21, 1992 (Box J3)
  - September 28, 1992 (Box J3)
  - October 5, 1992 (Box J3)
  - October 12, 1992 (Box J3)
  - October 19, 1992 (Box J3)
  - October 26, 1992 (Box J3)
  - November 2, 1992 (Box J3)
  - November 9, 1992 (Box J3)
  - November 16, 1992 (Box J3)
  - November 23, 1992 (Box J3)
  - December 7, 1992 (Box J3)
  - December 14, 1992 (Box J3)
  - January 11, 1993 (Box J4)
  - January, 18 1993 (Box J4)
  - January 25, 1993 (Box J4)
  - February 1, 1993 (Box J4)
  - February 8, 1993 (Box J4)
  - February 15, 1993 (Box J4)
  - March 1, 1993 (Box J4)
  - March 8, 1993 (Box J4)
  - March 15, 1993 (Box J4)
  - March 22, 1993 (Box J4)
  - March 29, 1993 (Box J4)
  - April 5, 1993 (Box J4)
  - April 12, 1993 (Box J4)
  - April 19, 1993 (Box J4)
  - April 26, 1993 (Box J4)
  - May 10, 1993 (Box J4)
  - May 24, 1993 (Box J4)
  - June 7, 1993 (Box J4)
  - June 21, 1993 (Box J4)
  - July 6, 1993 (Box J4)
  - July 19, 1993 (Box J4)
  - September 7, 1993 (Box J4)
  - September 13, 1993 (Box J4)
  - September 20, 1993 (Box J4)
  - September 27, 1993 (Box J4)
  - October 4, 1993 (Box J4)
  - October 11, 1993 (Box J4)
  - October 18, 1993 (Box J4)
  - October 25, 1993 (Box J4)
  - November 1, 1993 (Box J4)
  - November 8, 1993 (Box J4)
  - November 15, 1993 (Box J4)
  - November 22, 1993 (Box J4)
  - December 6, 1993 (Box J4)
  - December 13, 1993 (Box J4)
  - December 20, 1993 (Box J4)
  - January 10, 1994 (Box J4)
  - January 17, 1994 (Box J4)
  - January 24, 1994 (Box J4)
  - January 31, 1994 (Box J4)
  - February 7, 1994 (Box J4)
  - February 14, 1994 (Box J4)
  - February 28, 1994 (Box J4)
  - March 4, 1994 (Box J4)
  - March 7, 1994 (Box J4)
  - March 21, 1994 (Box J4)
  - March 28, 1994 (Box J4)
  - April 4, 1994 (Box J4)
  - April 11, 1994 (Box J4)
  - April 18, 1994 (Box J4)
  - April 25, 1994 (Box J4)
  - May 9, 1994 (Box J4)
  - May 23, 1994 (Box J4)
  - June 6, 1994 (Box J4)
  - June 20, 1994 (Box J4)
  - July 5, 1994 (Box J4)
  - July 18, 1994 (Box J4)
  - August 15, 1994 (Box J4)
  - September 6, 1994 (Box J5)
  - September 19, 1994 (Box J5)
  - September 26, 1994 (Box J5)
  - October 3, 1994 (Box J5)
  - October 10, 1994 (Box J5)
  - October 17, 1994 (Box J5)
  - October 24, 1994 (Box J5)
  - October 31, 1994 (Box J5)
  - November 7, 1994 (Box J5)
  - November 14, 1994 (Box J5)
  - November 21, 1994 (Box J5)
  - December 5, 1994 (Box J5)
  - December 12, 1994 (Box J5)
  - December 19, 1994 (Box J5)
  - January 9, 1995 (Box J5)
  - January 16, 1995 (Box J5)
  - January 23, 1995, 2 folders (Box J5)
    (includes extra prints)
  - January 30, 1995 (Box J5)
  - February 2, 1995 (Box J5)
  - February 13, 1995 (Box J5)
  - February 20, 1995 (Box J5)
  - March 6, 1995 (Box J5)
  - March 13, 1995 (Box J5)
  - March 20, 1995 (Box J5)
  - March 27, 1995 (Box J5)
  - April 3, 1995 (Box J5)
  - April 10, 1995 (Box J5)
  - April 17, 1995 (Box J5)
  - April 24, 1995 (Box J5)
  - May 8, 1995 (Box J5)
  - May 22, 1995 (Box J5)
  - June 19, 1995 (Box J5)
  - July 24, 1995 (Box J5)
  - September 25, 1995 (Box J5)
  - October 2, 1995 (Box J5)
  - October 9, 1995 (Box J5)
  - October 15, 1995 (Box J5)
  - October 30, 1995 (Box J5)
  - November 13, 1995 (Box J5)
  - December 5, 1995 (Box J5)
  - December 12, 1995 (Box J5)
  - December 19, 1995 (Box J5)
  - January 9, 1996 (Box J5)
  - January 16, 1996 (Box J5)
  - February 20, 1996 (Box J5)
  - February 27, 1996 (Box J5)
  - March 19, 1996 (Box J5)
  - March 26, 1996, 2 folders (Box J5)
    (includes prints not used)
  - July 9, 1996 (Box J5)
  - October 13, 1996 (Box J5)
  - October 29, 1996 (Box J5)
  - November 12, 1996 (Box J5)
  - November 26, 1996 (Box J5)
  - December 10, 1996 (Box J5)
  - January 7, 1997 (Box J5)
  - February 11, 1997 (Box J5)
  - February 25, 1997 (Box J5)
  - March 11, 1997 (Box J5)
  - March 18, 1997 (Box J5)
  - April 15, 1997 (Box J5)
  - April 22, 1997 (Box J5)
  - May 6, 1997 (Box J5)
  - June 10, 1997 (Box J5)
  - July 16, 1997 (Box J5)
  - July 30, 1997 (Box J5)
  - September 3, 1997 (Box J5)
  - September 10, 1997 (Box J5)
  - September 24, 1997 (Box J5)
  - February 25, 1998 (Box J5)
  - March and April, 1998 (Box J5)
  - September 1998 (Box J5)
  - Prints not Used (Box J6)
    - 1978-1983, 2 folders (Box J6)
    - 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box J6)
    - 1997-1998 (Box J6)